hondapartsnow.com 2009-12-05

# Buy Honda Parts and Accessories online at hondapartsnow.com - Honda Privacy Policy

Hondapartsnow.com, our most priority is ensuring that your personal and payment information is secure, and your privacy is respected. Below is a description of how we maintain online security and respect your privacy. **Online Security**  
When ever you provide any order information, we use SSL technology to make sure that it is "encrypted," or, scrambled, so that no one else can read it while it is being transmitted over the internet. If you become a member of hondapartsnow.com, all information (such as your name, address, and e-mail address) is safely stored behind a firewall. We store this type of information so that you do not have to reenter it each time you make a purchase or log in to use your account. **Online Privacy**  
This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the privacy policy pertaining to hondapartsnow.com (the "Site"). By using the Site, you are agreeing to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement. For purposes of this Privacy Policy Statement, "Personal Information" means any information by which you can be personally identified, and includes your name, your address, your telephone number, your e-mail address. Our site collects Personal Information only when you voluntarily submit such Personal Information to us, such as when placing a product order through the Site, when becoming a member of hondapartsnow.com, and so on. Hondapartsnow.com does not collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of thirteen, and if you are under thirteen, please give us the parental contact information or exit this site. For each visitor to the Site, our web servers automatically recognize information regarding the visitor's domain name (or that of the visitor's access provider) and e-mail address. Regardless of the purpose for which it is submitted, it is our (hondapartsnow.com) policy to maintain all Personal Information as confidential, and to use such Personal Information for the following purposes: 

  * For the specific purpose for which it was volunteered (Purchase products, enter contests)
  * To improve the content, appearance and utility of the site
  * To track our visitors' use of the site for internal market research or other business purposes
  * To notify our visitors of updates to the site

Our consumer list may also be shared with carefully selected firms whose products may be of interest to you. It is our (hondapartsnow.com) policy to keep Personal Information only for so long as needed for such purposes. At any time, you may obtain a summary of the Personal Information on record with hondapartsnow.com, which has been collected about you via this Site. Except for Personal Information we need to complete your purchase of products, you may request at any time that hondapartsnow.com dispose of any or all Personal Information about you. In addition, at any time you may request that hondapartsnow.com correct any such Personal Information or that such Personal Information be removed from our (hondapartsnow.com) marketing databases. To make any request described above, send an e-mail to service@hondapartsnow.com or write to: Hondapartsnow.com   
5838 Lankershim Blvd.   
North Hollywood, CA 91601 When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact e-mail address, name, addresses and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly. Consumer Service Call 800.813.4397 Monday - Saturday:  8am - 5pm PST Hondapartsnow.com reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy Statement at any time. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy Statement will mean that you accept those changes.
